<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Classroom Profiles docs</title>
    <link>https://digitalsoba.github.io/classroom-profiles-ops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Classroom Profiles docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:54:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://digitalsoba.github.io/classroom-profiles-ops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone</title>
      <link>https://digitalsoba.github.io/classroom-profiles-ops/ops/drone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 10:08:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalsoba.github.io/classroom-profiles-ops/ops/drone/</guid>
      <description>How to use and deploy Drone CICD Drone is an open source CI/CD tools that uses docker container for pipelines. It&amp;rsquo;s fast and highly configurable
Drone requirements: - Docker - Docker-compose - Github OAuth access
Create an OAuth App On Github, navigate to your Settings --&amp;gt; Developer Settings --&amp;gt; OAuth Apps. Create a new OAuth app. For both URLs we are using HTTPS because we will generate a Cert with Let’s Encrypt when drone is deployed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack</title>
      <link>https://digitalsoba.github.io/classroom-profiles-ops/ops/elastic-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 11:00:49 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalsoba.github.io/classroom-profiles-ops/ops/elastic-stack/</guid>
      <description>Intro The Elastic stack or ELK (Old nickname) is an open source set of tools that allow us to gather logs and metrics and visualize them. The main components of the include: Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana. Elastic Search is used to search, analyze, and store data. Logstash aggregates data into Elasticsearch. Kibana let&amp;rsquo;s use visualize our data. The stack also includes beats which are lightweight data shippers that point to either Elasticsearch or Logstash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Dev Environment</title>
      <link>https://digitalsoba.github.io/classroom-profiles-ops/basics/starting-dev-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:52:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalsoba.github.io/classroom-profiles-ops/basics/starting-dev-environment/</guid>
      <description>Classroom-Profiles 
COMP490/CIT480 Senior Design project. This application will navigate students to their respective classes based on their schedule and more!
How to get started with the project Prerequisites Make sure you have the following: - Git - A terminal - Docker - Docker-Compose - Composer - NPM or Yarn
Bootstrapping a freshly cloned project  Clone the repo into your projects folder with your terminal using git clone https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>